# IT INFRASTRUCTURE & SYSTEMS ADMINISTRATOR



# **ACCELLE** BUENO

#### **GET IN CONTACT**



Mobile: (+63) 977 749 0180



buenoaccelle@gmail.com



B 20 L 10, Casimiro Town Homes, Queens Row East, City of Bacoor, Cavite

#### PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a IT Infrastructure and Systems Administrator with 4+ years of experience in the field specializing in help desk support, Active Directory, and other administrative software. Adept at performing hardware and software upgrades and providing technical support to customers to resolve complex issues. Also, a part time Java programmer.

### **AREAS OF EXPERTISE**

- Active Directory (Add, Edit, Delete Users)
- Citrix Workspace
- Oracle Administration
- Google Suite/Workspace
- Java Programming
- Visual Basic Programming
- CISCO Basics (Routing & Switching)
- Computer and Network Troubleshooting
- MS Office Application (Excel, PowerPoint and Word)
- Ticketing System (OS Ticketing System, SysAid)
- Basic knowledge in Database Management System (MySQL & MS Access)
- Basic Web Design & Development (Bootstrap, Wordpress & Wix)
- Photo and Video Editing

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### IT INFRASTRUCTURE & SYSTEMS ADMINISTRATOR

Powersource OEG Services Inc. | October 2022 - Present Makati City, Manila

- Citrix Workspace administrator
- Google Workspace administrator
- Active directory administrator
- Oracle cloud administrator
- Network administrator
- Ensure security through access controls, backups and firewalls
- Performing on-site and off-site repairs, updates and maintenance on personal computers and related peripherals.
- Setting up and troubleshooting accounts and workstations.
- Responsible for tracking company it assets.
- Responsible for imaging and deploying all computer and software for the local site.
- Work with Procurement on maintaining and availing goods and services.
- · Monitor performance and maintain systems according to requirements.
- Build an internal wiki with technical documentation, manuals and it policies.
- Updates the company website and intranet.

## Java Developer

Freelancing | March 2022 - Present

#### Senior IT Support Specialist

Assurant BPO Company Solutions Inc. | Jan 2020 - Oct 2022 Pasay City, Metro Manila

- Performing on-site and off-site repairs and maintenance.
- Analyzing, diagnosing and resolving computer hardware, software, and network problems.
- Creating, Deleting and Editing logins on Active Directory.
- Monitoring ISP and client's equipment to make sure all equipment is within spec and charts.
- Responsible for assigning IP address and managing VLAN.
- Responsible for imaging and deploying all computer and software for the local site.
- Documenting and escalating cases to a higher level of support according to internal procedures.

#### OTHER SKILLS

- The ability to analyze complex technical information
- The ability to work well with people
- Detail oriented
- Customer Service
- Excellent problem solver
- Team Player
- Emotional Intelligence
- Leadership
- Positivity

#### **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

#### **IT STAFF**

Win Fortune Travel Agency Corporation | Sep 2019 - Jan 2020 Las Pinas, Metro Manila

- · Storing, retrieving, and manipulating data
- Modifying existing software to correct errors and optimize efficiency
- Monitoring and maintaining computer systems and networks
- Responding in a timely manner to service issues and requests
- Providing technical support across the company
- Repairing and replacing equipment as necessary
- Testing new technology

# **CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE**

Concentrix | Jun 2019 - Sep 2019

Alabang, Muntinlupa

- Handles incoming calls or inquiries from prospective customers or clients
- Assists customers effectively by solving customer disputes
- Provides customer additional information or explains services
- Discusses products offered and ensures customer satisfaction
- Handles confrontational or stressful interactions with the customer
- Creates and maintains service reports

## INTERNSHIP EXPERIENCE

#### IT INTERN

Assurant BPO Company Solutions Inc. | Jun 2018 - July 2018 Pasay City, Metro Manila

- Support the IT team in the maintenance of hardware, software and other systems
- Assist with troubleshooting issues and provide technical support
- Organize and maintain IT resources
- Lend IT support in areas such as cybersecurity, programming, analytics, and data center management

#### **EDUCATION HISTORY**

#### **CAVITE STATE UNIVERSITY - BACOOR CITY CAMPUS**

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology, 2019

• Best Thesis Awardee Rank 1, 2019

EASTERN BACOOR NATIONAL HIGH SCHOOL , CLASS 2015

QUEENS ROW ELEMENTARY SCHOOL, CLASS 2011